<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Blogs on Seyyid Dogan</title><link>https://seyahdoo.com/blog/</link><description>Recent content in Blogs on Seyyid Dogan</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://seyahdoo.com/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Games That I Recommend</title><link>https://seyahdoo.com/blog/game-recommendations/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://seyahdoo.com/blog/game-recommendations/</guid><description>Must Plays: Psychonauts 1 Psychonauts 2 Return of the Obra Dinn Celeste It Takes Two The Legend of Zelda: A Link to the Past We Were Here (whole franchise) Should Plays: Happenlance Sekiro Towerfall Ascension Remnant: From the Ashes Helldivers Starbound SteamWorld Dig 2 Trackmania(2020) Magicka Magicka 2 Heave Ho Nidhogg Lumino City &amp;amp; Lume INK Brütal Legend Life is Strange The Legend of Zelda: A Link Between Worlds The Legend of Zelda: Breath of the Wild FEZ Astroneer Risk of Rain 2 (with lots of mods) Golf with your friends Tabletop Simulator Arma 3 (with an arma clan, with lots of mods, never play alone)</description></item><item><title>Installing QMK on Keychron k3v2 RGB with optical switches</title><link>https://seyahdoo.com/blog/qmk-on-keychron-k3v2/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://seyahdoo.com/blog/qmk-on-keychron-k3v2/</guid><description>Disclaimer: Bluetooth connectivity will not work after this modification After I did this modification my keyboard is sometimes not working after plugging in. I have to plug in several times to make it work sometimes. See the hack below. How to do it: Using this guide; https://sonixqmk.github.io//SonixDocs/install/
Setup QMK environment with Sonix QMK repo Download &amp;ldquo;Sonix Keyboard Flasher&amp;rdquo; [HACK] Checkout chibios-contrib to commit d5e4fb2517b47a6a507fb765d3c78ea46b80f430 (this is a hack to solve the keyboard not working sometimes when you plug in) Compile QMK Sonix fimware; This is command for Keychron k3v2 with RGB qmk compile -kb keychron/k3/rgb/optical_iso -km iso And here is how my output looks like on a successfull run Ψ Compiling keymap with make --jobs=1 keychron/k3/rgb/optical_iso:via_iso QMK Firmware 0.</description></item></channel></rss>