<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Blogs on Seyyid Dogan</title><link>https://seyahdoo.com/blog/</link><description>Recent content in Blogs on Seyyid Dogan</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://seyahdoo.com/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Pixel 5 Imei Repair Guide</title><link>https://seyahdoo.com/blog/pixel-5-imei-repair/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://seyahdoo.com/blog/pixel-5-imei-repair/</guid><description>The Reason The info on how to repair imei on pixel 5 is quite sparse and I needed a day of hacking around to actually do it. Im writing this guide to maybe help another soul that is on this same journey for some reason. Hopefully this helps. Have a great day fella &amp;lt;3
How To do It - unlock bootloader (this will wipe the device, make sure you have backup) - downgrade the system to earliest possible firmware (redfin-rd1a.</description></item><item><title>We Glock G17 Gen 4 Magazine Release Spring Fix</title><link>https://seyahdoo.com/blog/we-glock-g17-gen4-mag-release-spring-fix/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://seyahdoo.com/blog/we-glock-g17-gen4-mag-release-spring-fix/</guid><description>Intro The We Glock G17 Gen 4 has a chronic problem. It sometimes fails to catch the magazine, even if the magazine is fully inserted. And this will lead to magazines being left on the field and no mag being on the replica while we most need it. Certainly a dire situation that needs fixing.
The Problem The problem certainly arises from the magazine catch spring. If we need that satisfying click and a firm hold on the magazine.</description></item><item><title>Retevis RA685 Type C Port Fix</title><link>https://seyahdoo.com/blog/retevis-ra685-type-c-fix/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://seyahdoo.com/blog/retevis-ra685-type-c-fix/</guid><description>Intro So I bought this radio, with type-c port for charging, expecting it to work as normal and fine. But the type c port on Retevis RA685 does not work with type-c to type-c cables. So I had to diagnose the issue, learn how to fix it and buy some tools to getthe job done. Here is how I did it.
The Problem The problem with the port is that it is only connected to VCC and Ground.</description></item><item><title>Windows Mods &amp; Programs</title><link>https://seyahdoo.com/blog/windows_mods/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://seyahdoo.com/blog/windows_mods/</guid><description>Posy&amp;rsquo;s Mouse Cursor (default one) Because the windows default one is crooked and does not look right, I changed my mouse cursor to this.
http://www.michieldb.nl/other/cursors/
Turkish programmers layout (my own keyboard layout) https://github.com/seyahdoo/turkish-programmer-keyboard-layout
Autohotkey and Python scripts for stuff and Launchy or Steamdeck to launch them (no longer used) https://github.com/seyahdoo/AHK Win 10 LTSB A really stripped down and stable version of windows 10. It does not have most of the bloatware and it receives updates 1 year after the main channel.</description></item><item><title>Stuff that I have modded</title><link>https://seyahdoo.com/blog/my_mods/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://seyahdoo.com/blog/my_mods/</guid><description>To be filled in later&amp;hellip;
Keyboard Phone Windows Autohotkey mods Launchy Streamdeck Pmdeck Git IDE (Rider) Risk of Rain 2 Mobge Unity CI Window Laps Framework (Its so modded that its no longer a mod) My own hitbox game controller</description></item><item><title>Games That I Recommend</title><link>https://seyahdoo.com/blog/game-recommendations/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://seyahdoo.com/blog/game-recommendations/</guid><description>Must Plays: Psychonauts 1 Psychonauts 2 Return of the Obra Dinn The Case of the Golden Idol Celeste (The 2020 Celeste Spring Community Collab and The Secret of Celeste Mountain looks great if you have finished the base game) It Takes Two The Legend of Zelda: A Link to the Past We Were Here (whole franchise) A Short Hike Hi-Fi Rush Inscryption Should Plays: Kena: Bridge of Spirits Happenlance Sekiro Towerfall Ascension Remnant: From the Ashes Helldivers Starbound SteamWorld Dig 2 Trackmania(2020, United Forever) Magicka Magicka 2 Heave Ho Nidhogg Lumino City &amp;amp; Lume INK Brütal Legend Life is Strange The Legend of Zelda: A Link Between Worlds The Legend of Zelda: Breath of the Wild The Legend of Zelda: Tears of the Kingdom FEZ Astroneer Risk of Rain 2 (with lots of mods) Golf It Tabletop Simulator Arma 3 (with an arma clan, with lots of mods, never play alone)</description></item><item><title>Installing QMK on Keychron k3v2 RGB with optical switches</title><link>https://seyahdoo.com/blog/qmk-on-keychron-k3v2/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://seyahdoo.com/blog/qmk-on-keychron-k3v2/</guid><description>Disclaimer: Bluetooth connectivity will not work after this modification On my system, when you first plug the usb cable, it almost never connects at the first time; I&amp;rsquo;ve added #define NO_USB_STARTUP_CHECK = yes to the config.h to fix it. I&amp;rsquo;m really not sure why this fixes it but I&amp;rsquo;ve got the idea from here. &amp;gt; https://github.com/qmk/qmk_firmware/issues/5585 How to do it: Using this guide; https://sonixqmk.github.io//SonixDocs/install/
Setup QMK environment with Sonix QMK repo Apply config and keymap files Download &amp;ldquo;Sonix Keyboard Flasher&amp;rdquo; Compile QMK Sonix fimware with this command -&amp;gt; qmk compile -kb keychron/k3/rgb/optical_iso -km iso Binary is at your home &amp;ldquo;qmk_firmware&amp;rdquo; folder and named with &amp;ldquo;.</description></item></channel></rss>