<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Diy on Bahar Doğan</title><link>https://seyahdoo.com/tags/diy/</link><description>Recent content in Diy on Bahar Doğan</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://seyahdoo.com/tags/diy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>We Glock G17 Gen 4 Magazine Release Spring Fix</title><link>https://seyahdoo.com/blog/we-glock-g17-gen4-mag-release-spring-fix/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://seyahdoo.com/blog/we-glock-g17-gen4-mag-release-spring-fix/</guid><description>&lt;h3 id="intro">Intro&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>The We Glock G17 Gen 4 has a chronic problem. It sometimes fails to catch the magazine, even if the magazine is fully inserted.
And this will lead to magazines being left on the field and no mag being on the replica while we most need it.
Certainly a dire situation that needs fixing.&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="the-problem">The Problem&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>The problem certainly arises from the magazine catch spring. If we need that satisfying click and a firm hold on the magazine.
We need a stronger spring on the magazine catch assembly.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Retevis RA685 Type C Port Fix</title><link>https://seyahdoo.com/blog/retevis-ra685-type-c-fix/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://seyahdoo.com/blog/retevis-ra685-type-c-fix/</guid><description>&lt;h3 id="intro">Intro&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>So I bought this radio, with type-c port for charging, expecting it to work as normal and fine. But the type c port on Retevis RA685 does not work with type-c to type-c cables.
So I had to diagnose the issue, learn how to fix it and buy some tools to getthe job done. Here is how I did it.&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="the-problem">The Problem&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>The problem with the port is that it is only connected to VCC and Ground.
This means when a usb c device is connected, the host device has no way of knowing the cable orientation or if anything is plugged in at all.
So type c hosts, by default will not provide power to this device.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>